Finding Aid for Clare E. Hoffman Papers 1934-1962
Bentley Historical Library, University of Michigan
- General Files 1944-1962, 21.5 linear feet
  - 1946
    - Taylor, Arthur C. (Box 9)
    - Truman's speech of January 3 (Box 9)
    - U (miscellaneous) (Box 9)
    - Unions (general) (Box 9)
    - V (miscellaneous) (Box 9)
    - W (miscellaneous) (Box 9)
    - Weekly News Letter (Box 9)
  - 1947-1948
    - A (miscellaneous) (Box 9)
    - Adverse
      - In district (Box 9)
      - Out of district (Box 9)
    - American Federation of Labor (communications with) (Box 9)
    - American Vigilant Intelligence Federation (Harry A. Jung) (Box 9)
    - Ayers, Claude W. (Box 9)
    - B (miscellaneous) (Box 9)
    - Bacheller, Hazel (Box 9)
    - Bostetter, M.J. (National Carbon Coated Paper Co.) (Box 9)
    - Boyd, L.A. (Boyd's Orchard Pack) (Box 9)
    - Brady, Aubrey (Box 9)
    - Broker, William (Box 9)
    - Burnette, William A. (Burnette Castings Co.), 3 folders (Box 9)
    - Burnette Castings Co.: proposed NLRB investigation, 2 folders (Box 9)
    - C (miscellaneous) (Box 9)
    - Camfield, Alfred B. (Paw Paw, Michigan, correspondent) (Box 9)
    - Close, Upton-Gerald Winrod (Box 9)
    - Commendatory
      - In district (Box 9)
      - Out of district (Box 9)
    - Communists - Communism (Box 9)
    - Complaints (Box 10)
      - Labor Department (Box 10)
      - Unions (Box 10)
      - Miscellaneous, 2 folders (Box 10)
    - Conference of American Small Business Organizations (Box 10)
    - Congress of Industrial Organizations (and affiliates) (Box 10)
    - Constitutional Educational League (Joseph P. Kamp) (Box 10)
    - D (miscellaneous) (Box 10)
    - E (miscellaneous) (Box 10)
    - F (miscellaneous) (Box 10)
    - G (miscellaneous) (Box 10)
    - Granger, F.L. (Producers Service Corporation) (Box 10)
    - H (miscellaneous) (Box 10)
    - Hadsell, Philip A. (Box 10)
    - Hamilton Farm Bureau (Box 10)
    - Harrah, W.F. (National-Standard Co., Niles, Michigan) (Box 10)
    - Hill, R.L. (Box 10)
    - Hoffman House Talks: responses to speeches and requests for copies (Box 10)
    - Hoffman Radio Talks: responses to speeches and requests for copies
      - January 14, 1947, January 28, 1947 (Box 10)
      - March 9, 1947 (Box 10)
      - March 11, 1947 (aid to Greece) (Box 10)
      - April 20, 1947 (Box 10)
      - May 24, 1947 (pending labor legislation) (Box 10)
      - May 25, 1947 discussion of labor legislation on Blair Moody's "Meet Your Congressman" program (Box 10)
      - April 14, 1948 (Box 10)
      - April 28, 1948 (Box 10)
    - I (miscellaneous) (Box 10)
    - Invitations (Box 10)
    - J (miscellaneous) (Box 10)
    - Jewish (Box 10)
    - Jones, A.L. (Box 10)
    - K (miscellaneous) (Box 10)
    - Knowles, Beatrice M. (Box 10)
    - L (miscellaneous) (Box 10)
    - Law (Box 10)
    - Lillie, Leo C. (Box 10)
    - Luttrell, R.E. (Box 10)
    - M (miscellaneous) (Box 10)
    - Mc (miscellaneous) (Box 10)
    - McGarity, R.P. (Berrien Real Estate Service, Three Rivers, Michigan) (Box 10)
    - N (miscellaneous) (Box 10)
    - News Letters (Box 10)
    - Newhouse, Walter (Saranac Machine Co., Benton Harbor, Michigan) (Box 10)
    - Newspapers
      - In district (Box 10)
      - Out of district (Box 11)
    - O (miscellaneous) (Box 11)
    - P (miscellaneous) (Box 11)
    - Pomeroy, Paul D. (Box 11)
    - Questionnaires (rarely completed, but with occasional information) (Box 11)
    - R (miscellaneous) (Box 11)
    - S (miscellaneous) (Box 11)
    - South Haven Fruit Exchange (Box 11)
    - Speaking Engagements (Box 11)
    - Stickler, C.L. (Box 11)
    - T (miscellaneous) (Box 11)
    - Taylor, Arthur C. (Box 11)
    - Thomas, W. D. (Box 11)
    - Twyeffort, Raymond G. (Box 11)
    - U (miscellaneous) (Box 11)
    - Unions (general) (Box 11)
    - V (miscellaneous) (Box 11)
    - W (miscellaneous) (Box 11)
  - 1949-1950
    - A (miscellaneous) (Box 11)
    - Adverse
      - In district (Box 11)
      - Out of district (Box 11)
    - American Federation of Labor (communications with) (Box 11)
    - American Vigilant Intelligence Federation (Harry A. Jung) (Box 11)
    - Ayers, Claude W. (Box 11)
    - B (miscellaneous) (Box 11)
    - Blanchard, A.G. (Box 11)
    - Bostetter, M.J. (Box 11)
    - Boyd, L.A. (Box 11)
    - Brady, Aubrey (Box 11)
    - Burnette, William A. (Burnette Castings Co.), 2 folders (Box 11)
    - C (miscellaneous) (Box 11)
    - Camfield, Alfred B. (Box 11)
    - Commendatory
      - In district (Box 11)
      - Out of district (Box 12)
      - Marine Corps article (Box 12)
    - Communists - Communism (Box 12)
    - Complaints
      - Army (Box 12)
      - Coal (Box 12)
      - Truman (Box 12)
      - Miscellaneous, 2 folders (Box 12)
    - Congress of Industrial Organizations (and affiliates) (Box 12)
    - Constitutional Educational League (Joseph P. Kamp) (Box 12)
    - D (miscellaneous) (Box 12)
    - Dubuisson, A.D. (Box 12)
    - Dukesherer, Ed (Box 12)
    - E (miscellaneous) (Box 12)
    - F (miscellaneous) (Box 12)
    - FBI (J. Edgar Hoover) (Box 12)
    - G (miscellaneous) (Box 12)
    - Granger, F.L. (Producers Service Corporation) (Box 12)
    - H (miscellaneous) (Box 12)
    - Harrah, W.F. (National-Standard Co., Niles, Michigan) (Box 12)
    - Heuer, Harold M. (National Motor Casting Division) (Box 12)
    - Hill, R.L. (Box 12)
    - Hoffman House Talks (responses to speeches and requests for copies)
      - Coal Strike February 20, 1950 (Box 12)
      - Misuse of Hoover Label (Plan No. 12) March 30, 1950 (Box 12)
      - Steel Board (Box 12)
      - Miscellaneous (Box 12)
    - Hoffman Radio and Television Talks
      - January 24, 1949 (Box 12)
      - March 27, 1949 (Box 12)
      - February 3, 1950 (Box 12)
      - Miscellaneous (Box 12)
    - Hoffman Reprints (Box 12)
    - Invitations (Box 12)
    - J (miscellaneous) (Box 13)
    - Jewish (Box 13)
    - Jones, A.L. (Armstrong Machine Works) (Box 13)
    - K (miscellaneous) (Box 13)
    - Knowles, Beatrice M. (Box 13)
    - L (miscellaneous) (Box 13)
    - M (miscellaneous) (Box 13)
    - Mc (miscellaneous) (Box 13)
    - McGarity, R.P. (Box 13)
    - McLaughlin, J.H. (Box 13)
    - Miller, Walter (New Products Corp., Benton Harbor, Michigan) (Box 13)
    - Miscellaneous (Box 13)
    - N (miscellaneous) (Box 13)
    - News Letters, 2 folders (Box 13)
    - Newhouse, Walter (Saranac Machine Co., Benton Harbor, Michigan) (Box 13)
    - Newspapers
      - In district (Box 13)
      - Out of district (Box 13)
    - O (miscellaneous) (Box 13)
    - P (miscellaneous) (Box 13)
    - Petersen, A. Scott (Box 13)
    - Pomeroy, Paul D. (Box 13)
    - Potts, J. Fred (Box 13)
    - Q (miscellaneous) (Box 13)
    - Questionnaires (Rarely completed, but with occasional information) (Box 13)
    - R (miscellaneous) (Box 13)
    - Schouten, John H. (Box 13)
    - South Haven Fruit Exchange (Cornelius Bus, manager) (Box 13)
    - Speaking Engagements (Box 13)
    - Sullivan, George E. (Washington, D.C. attorney) (Box 13)
    - T (miscellaneous) (Box 13)
    - Taylor, Arthur C. (Box 13)
    - Thomas, W.D. (Box 13)
    - U (miscellaneous) (Box 13)
    - V (miscellaneous) (Box 13)
    - W (miscellaneous) (Box 13)
  - 1951-1952
    - A (miscellaneous) (Box 13)
    - Adverse
      - In district (Box 13)
      - Out of district (Box 13)
    - American Vigilant Intelligence Federation (Harry A. Jung) (Box 13)
    - B (miscellaneous) (Box 13)
    - Banyon, Stanley (Benton Harbor News-Palladium) (Box 13)
    - Boyd, L.A. (Boyd's Orchard Pack) (Box 13)
    - Brady, Aubrey (Box 13)
    - Broker, William (Box 13)
    - Burnette, William A. (Pan American Sales Company) (Box 13)
    - Bus, Cornelius (South Haven Fruit Exchange) (Box 13)
    - C (miscellaneous) (Box 14)
    - Camfield, Alfred B. (Box 14)
    - Christie, Hugh (Box 14)
    - Commendatory
      - In district (Box 14)
      - Out of district (Box 14)
    - Committee for Constitutional Government (Box 14)
    - Communists - Communism (Box 14)
    - Complaints
      - Administration, 4 folders (Box 14)
      - Defense Establishment (Box 14)
      - Departments (Box 14)
      - Miscellaneous (Box 14)
    - Congress of Industrial Organizations (and affiliates) (Box 14)
    - Constitutional Educational League (Box 14)
    - D (miscellaneous) (Box 14)
    - Donner, Robert (Box 14)
    - F (miscellaneous) (Box 14)
    - G (miscellaneous) (Box 14)
    - Granger, F.L. (Producers Service Corp.) (Box 14)
    - H (miscellaneous) (Box 14)
    - Harrah, W.F. (National-Standard Co., Niles, Michigan) (Box 14)
    - Hill, R. L. (Box 14)
    - Hoffman House Talks (responses to speeches and requests for copies)
      - January 9, 1951 (Thomas Dewey) (Box 14)
      - Various dates (Foreign Policy) (Box 14)
      - September 1951 (Salary cut) (Box 14)
      - October 8, 1951 (Truman Security Order) (Box 15)
      - October 20, 1951 (Joseph Kamp) (Box 15)
      - February 25, 1952 (Box 15)
      - General (Box 15)
    - Hoffman Radio Talks (Box 15)
    - I (miscellaneous) (Box 15)
    - Invitations (Box 15)
    - J (miscellaneous) (Box 15)
    - Johnson, Aben (Box 15)
    - Jones, A.L. (Armstrong Machine Works, Three Rivers, Michigan) (Box 15)
    - K (miscellaneous) (Box 15)
    - Knowles, Beatrice M. (Box 15)
    - L (miscellaneous) (Box 15)
    - Lavely, S.D. (Independent Voters League) (Box 15)
    - Lewis, Fulton (Box 15)
    - M (miscellaneous) (Box 15)
    - Mc (miscellaneous) (Box 15)
    - McGarity, R.P. (Box 15)
    - Miller, Walter (Box 15)
    - N (miscellaneous) (Box 15)
    - News Letters (Box 15)
    - Newhouse, Walter (Saranac Machine Co.) (Box 15)
    - Newspapers
      - In district (Box 15)
      - Out of district (Box 15)
    - O (miscellaneous) (Box 15)
    - P (miscellaneous) (Box 15)
    - Pomeroy, Paul D. (Box 15)
    - Potts, J. Fred (Box 15)
    - Prayer, Day of (Box 15)
    - Q (miscellaneous) (Box 15)
    - Questionnaires (Rarely completed, but with occasional information) (Box 15)
    - R (miscellaneous) (Box 15)
    - S (miscellaneous) (Box 15)
    - Sayre, Homer D. (Box 15)
    - South Haven Fruit Exchange (Box 15)
    - Speaking Engagements (Box 15)
    - T (miscellaneous) (Box 15)
    - Taylor, Arthur C. (Box 15)
    - Thomas, W.D. (Box 16)
    - Unions (general) (Box 16)
    - V (miscellaneous) (Box 16)
    - W (miscellaneous) (Box 16)
    - Wells, Maurice A. (Harvey Paper Products, Sturgis, Michigan) (Box 16)
  - 1953-1954
    - A (miscellaneous) (Box 16)
    - Adverse
      - In district (Box 16)
      - Out of district (Box 16)
    - Allegan State Bank (Box 16)
    - American Vigilant Intelligence Federation (Harry A. Jung) (Box 16)
    - Ayers, Claude W. (Box 16)
    - B (miscellaneous) (Box 16)
    - Bethune, Mrs. N. (Box 16)
    - Boyd, L.A. (Boyd's Orchard Pack) (Box 16)
    - Brady, Aubrey (Box 16)
    - Broker, William (Box 16)
    - C (miscellaneous) (Box 16)
    - Cain, Thomas W. (Box 16)
    - Camfield, Alfred B. (Box 16)
    - Chesebro, Allen (Box 16)
    - Christie, Hugh (Box 16)
    - Commendatory
      - In district (Box 16)
      - Out of district (Box 16)
    - Committee for Constitutional Government (Box 16)
    - Communists - Communism (Box 16)
    - Complaints
      - Administration (Box 16)
      - Defense Establishment (Box 16)
      - Departments (Box 16)
      - Income Taxes (Box 16)
      - Railroad Retirement Board (Box 16)
      - Miscellaneous (Box 16)
    - Congress of Industrial Organizations (and affiliates) (Box 16)
    - Constitutional Educational League (Box 16)
    - Cowling, F.J. (Box 16)
    - D (miscellaneous) (Box 16)
    - Donner, Robert (Box 16)
    - F (miscellaneous) (Box 16)
    - G (miscellaneous) (Box 16)
    - Granger, F.L. (Producers Service Corp.) (Box 16)
    - H (miscellaneous) (Box 16)
    - Harrah, C.C. (Duke Harrah, Inc., Niles, Michigan) (Box 17)
    - Harrah, W. F. (National Standard Co.) (Box 17)
    - Hart, Mervin K. (Box 17)
    - Hill, R.L. (Box 17)
    - Hoffman Talks (Box 17)
    - Hoffman Radio Talks (Box 17)
    - I (miscellaneous) (Box 17)
    - Invitations (selection) (Box 17)
    - J (miscellaneous) (Box 17)
    - Johnson, Aben (Box 17)
    - Jones, Arthur L. (Armstrong Machine Works, Three Rivers, Michigan) (Box 17)
    - K (miscellaneous) (Box 17)
    - Knowles, Beatrice M. (Box 17)
    - L (miscellaneous) (Box 17)
    - Lavely, S.D (Box 17)
      (Independent Voters League, Watervliet, Michigan)
    - M (miscellaneous) (Box 17)
    - Mc (miscellaneous) (Box 17)
    - McCarthy, Joseph (about) (Box 17)
    - McGarity, R.P. (Box 17)
    - Miller, Walter (Box 17)
    - N (miscellaneous) (Box 17)
    - National Labor Relations Board (Box 17)
    - New Deal (Box 17)
    - Newhouse, Walter (Box 17)
    - News Letters (Box 17)
    - Newspapers and radio stations
      - In district (arranged alphabetically), 12 folders (Box 17)
      - Out of district (Box 17)
    - O (miscellaneous) (Box 17)
    - Overton, Glen (Overton Machine co., Allegan) (Box 17)
    - P (miscellaneous) (Box 17)
    - Peters, Paul O. (Box 17)
    - Pomeroy, Paul D. (Box 17)
    - Potts, J. Fred (Box 17)
    - R (miscellaneous) (Box 17)
    - S (miscellaneous) (Box 17)
    - Salsbury, Buel (Box 18)
    - Scott, Hugh (speech and CEH reaction) (Box 18)
    - Speaking Engagements (Box 18)
    - Stickler, C.L. (Box 18)
    - T (miscellaneous) (Box 18)
    - Thomas, W.D. (Box 18)
    - Unions (general) (Box 18)
    - V (miscellaneous) (Box 18)
    - W (miscellaneous) (Box 18)
    - Waldron, C.L. (Box 18)
    - Wells, Maurice A. (Box 18)
    - Wells Manufacturing Corp., Three Rivers, Michigan (Box 18)
    - Whirlpool Corp. (Box 18)
    - Wood, John T. (Box 18)
    - XYZ (miscellaneous) (Box 18)
  - 1955-1956
    - A (miscellaneous) (Box 18)
    - Adverse
      - In district (Box 18)
      - Out of district (Box 18)
    - Ayers, Claude W. (Box 18)
    - B (miscellaneous) (Box 18)
    - Bethune, Nagene (Box 18)
    - Boyd, L.A. (Box 18)
    - Brady, Aubrey (Box 18)
    - Burnette, William A. (Box 18)
    - C (miscellaneous) (Box 18)
    - Cain, Thomas W. (Box 18)
    - Camfield, Alfred B. (Box 18)
    - Carmody, M.V. (Box 18)
    - Christie, Hugh (Box 18)
    - Clardy, Kit (Box 18)
    - Commendatory
      - In district (Box 18)
      - Out of district (Box 18)
    - Committee for Constitutional Government (Box 18)
    - Communists - Communism (Box 18)
    - Complaints
      - Administration (Box 18)
      - Defense Establishment (Box 18)
      - Departments (Box 18)
      - Miscellaneous (Box 18)
    - Constitutional Educational League (Box 18)
    - D (miscellaneous) (Box 18)
    - E (miscellaneous) (Box 18)
    - F (miscellaneous) (Box 18)
    - Fletcher, Joseph H. (Box 18)
    - G (miscellaneous) (Box 18)
    - Granger, F.L. (Box 18)
    - H (miscellaneous) (Box 18)
    - Hamlin, Barbara (Box 18)
    - Harrah, C.C. (Box 18)
    - Harrah, W.F. (National Standard Co., Niles, Michigan) (Box 18)
    - Hart, Mervin K. (Box 18)
    - Hill, R.L. (Box 18)
    - Hoffman House Talks (Box 19)
      - General (Box 19)
      - Walter Reuther speech (selection taken), 3 folders (Box 19)
    - Hoffman Radio Talks (Box 19)
    - Hoffman Releases (general) (Box 19)
    - Holmes, J.S. (St. Joseph, Michigan, correspondent) (Box 19)
    - I (miscellaneous) (Box 19)
    - Invitations (selection taken), 2 folders (Box 19)
    - Isham, Mary E. (Box 19)
    - J (miscellaneous) (Box 19)
    - Johnson, Aben (Box 19)
    - Jones, Arthur L. (Box 19)
    - K (miscellaneous) (Box 19)
    - Knowles, Beatrice M. (Box 19)
    - L (miscellaneous) (Box 19)
    - Lavely, S.D. (Box 19)
    - M (miscellaneous) (Box 19)
    - Mc (miscellaneous) (Box 19)
    - McCarthy, Joseph (about) (Box 19)
    - McGarity, R.P. (Box 19)
    - McKenna, William F. (Box 19)
    - Merwin, Davis (Box 19)
    - Montgomery, W. (Edwardsburg, Michigan, clergyman) (Box 19)
    - N (miscellaneous) (Box 19)
    - Newhouse, Walter (Box 19)
    - Newsletters (Box 19)
    - Newspapers
      - In district, 10 folders (Box 19)
      - Out of district (Box 19)
    - O (miscellaneous) (Box 19)
    - P (miscellaneous) (Box 19)
    - Pomeroy, Paul D. (Box 19)
    - Potts, J. Fred (Box 19)
    - Prairie River (Box 19)
    - R (miscellaneous) (Box 19)
    - Radio Stations (Box 19)
    - Rawson, Al (Box 19)
    - Robinson, G.D. (Box 19)
    - S (miscellaneous) (Box 19)
    - Speaking Engagements (Box 19)
    - T (miscellaneous) (Box 20)
    - U (miscellaneous) (Box 20)
    - Unemployment (Box 20)
    - Union Now (Box 20)
    - Unions, 2 folders (Box 20)
    - V (miscellaneous) (Box 20)
    - W (miscellaneous) (Box 20)
    - Waldron, C.L. (Box 20)
    - Whirlpool Corp. (Box 20)
    - Wood, Junius B. (Box 20)
    - Woodward, J.W. (Box 20)
  - 1957-1958
    - A (miscellaneous) (Box 20)
    - Adverse
      - In district (Box 20)
      - Out of district (Box 20)
    - Ayers, Claude W. (Box 20)
    - B (miscellaneous) (Box 20)
    - Boyd, L.A. (Box 20)
    - Brady, Aubrey (Box 20)
    - C (miscellaneous) (Box 20)
    - Chamber of Commerce (Box 20)
    - Christie, Hugh (Box 20)
    - Clardy, Kit (Box 20)
    - Commendatory
      - In district (Box 20)
      - Out of district (Box 20)
    - Committee for Constitutional Government (Box 20)
    - Communists-Communism (Box 20)
    - Complaints
      - Administration (Box 20)
      - Defense Establishment (Box 20)
      - Departments (Box 20)
      - Miscellaneous (Box 20)
    - Constitutional Educational League (Box 20)
    - D (miscellaneous) (Box 20)
    - Detroit Edison Company (Box 20)
    - F (miscellaneous) (Box 20)
    - Fletcher, Joseph H. (Box 20)
    - G (miscellaneous) (Box 20)
    - Granger, F.L. (Box 20)
    - H (miscellaneous) (Box 20)
    - Hagenstein, W.D. (Box 20)
    - Harrah, C.C. (Box 20)
    - Harrah, W.F. (Box 20)
    - Heuer, H.M. (Box 20)
    - Hicks, Hazel (Box 20)
    - Hill, R.L. (Box 20)
    - Hoffman House Talks
      - General (Box 20)
      - McCarthy, Joseph (Box 20)
      - Reuther, Walter (selection) (Box 20)
    - Hoffman Radio Talks (Box 20)
    - Hoffman Speeches (Box 20)
    - Hoffman Television Appearances (Box 20)
    - Holmes, J.S. (Box 21)
    - Integration (Box 21)
    - Invitations (selection taken), 2 folders (Box 21)
    - Isham, Mary E. (Box 21)
    - J (miscellaneous) (Box 21)
    - Johnson, Aben (Box 21)
    - K (miscellaneous) (Box 21)
    - Knowles, Beatrice M. (Box 21)
    - Kohler company (Box 21)
    - Koloseik, Carl M. (Box 21)
    - M (miscellaneous) (Box 21)
    - McGarity, R.P. (Box 21)
    - McKenna, William F. (Box 21)
    - Manion, Clarence (Dean) (Box 21)
    - Missiles (Box 21)
    - Montgomery, W. (Rev.) (Box 21)
    - N (miscellaneous) (Box 21)
    - Newhouse, Walter (Box 21)
    - Newsletters (Box 21)
    - Newspapers
      - In district, 10 folders (Box 21)
      - Out of district (Box 21)
    - Nicholas, George E. (Box 21)
    - O (miscellaneous) (Box 21)
    - P (miscellaneous) (Box 21)
    - Pomeroy, Paul D. (Box 21)
    - Questionnaires (Rarely completed, but with occasional information) (Box 21)
    - R (miscellaneous) (Box 21)
    - Radio Stations, 2 folders (Box 21)
    - Rawson, Al (Box 21)
    - Richer, Menno (Box 21)
    - Richmond, Vincent (Box 21)
    - Robinson, Gordon D. (Box 21)
    - S (miscellaneous) (Box 21)
    - St. Joseph-Benton Harbor (Box 21)
    - Salsbury, Buel (Box 21)
    - Schouten, John H. (Box 21)
    - Segregation (Box 21)
    - Smith, Florence (Box 21)
    - Speaking Engagements (Box 21)
    - Stickler, C.L. (Box 21)
    - Supreme Court (Box 21)
    - T (miscellaneous) (Box 21)
    - Television Stations (Box 21)
    - Unions (general) (Box 22)
    - Van Osdoll, C.W. (Box 22)
    - W (miscellaneous) (Box 22)
    - Whirlpool Seeger Corp. (Box 22)
    - Woodward, J.W. (Box 22)
  - 1959-1960
    - A (miscellaneous) (Box 22)
    - Adverse
      - In district (Box 22)
      - Out of district (Box 22)
    - Allegan (City) (Box 22)
    - Ayers, Claude W. (Box 22)
    - B (miscellaneous) (Box 22)
    - Borush, John (Box 22)
    - Boyd, L.A. (Box 22)
    - Brady, Aubrey (Box 22)
    - Butts, Eugene R. (Box 22)
    - C (miscellaneous) (Box 22)
    - Campbell, Keith (Box 22)
    - Christie, Hugh (Box 22)
    - Commendatory
      - In district (Box 22)
      - Out of district (Box 22)
    - Committee for Constitutional Government (Box 22)
    - Communists-Communism (Box 22)
    - Complaints
      - Administration (Box 22)
      - Departments (Box 22)
      - Miscellaneous (Box 22)
    - Constitutional Educational League (Box 22)
    - Curran, Joseph (Box 22)
    - D (miscellaneous) (Box 22)
    - E (miscellaneous) (Box 22)
    - F (miscellaneous) (Box 22)
    - Fletcher, Joseph H. (Box 22)
    - G (miscellaneous) (Box 22)
    - Granger, F.L. (Box 22)
    - H (miscellaneous) (Box 22)
    - Harrah, C.C. (Box 22)
    - Harrah, W.F. (Box 22)
    - Hart, Merwin K. (Box 22)
    - Heibel, Cletus (Box 22)
    - Hicks, hazel (Box 22)
    - Hill, R.L. (Box 22)
    - Hoffman House Talks
      - General (Box 22)
      - Adverse comment (Box 22)
      - Kennedy, Robert F., "The Enemy Within" (Box 22)
      - Lynching (Box 22)
      - Reuther, Walter, 2 folders (Box 22)
    - Hoffman Opinion (Box 23)
    - Hoffman Television Appearances (Box 23)
    - Hoffman Votes (Box 23)
    - Holmes, J.S. (Box 23)
    - Ideas (Box 23)
    - Invitations (selection taken), 2 folders (Box 23)
    - J (miscellaneous) (Box 23)
    - Johnson, Aben (Hastings Manufacturing Co.) (Box 23)
    - K (miscellaneous) (Box 23)
    - Kohler Company (Box 23)
    - Koloseik, Carl (Box 23)
    - L (miscellaneous) (Box 23)
    - M (miscellaneous) (Box 23)
    - Mc (miscellaneous) (Box 23)
    - McGarity, R.P. (Box 23)
    - McKenna, William F. (Box 23)
    - N (miscellaneous) (Box 23)
    - Nepotism (Box 23)
    - Newhouse, Walter (Box 23)
    - Newsletters (selection) (Box 23)
    - Newspapers
      - In district, 9 folders (Box 23)
      - Out of district (Box 23)
    - P (miscellaneous) (Box 23)
    - Pomeroy, Paul D. (Box 23)
    - Potts, J. Fred (Box 23)
    - Questionnaires (Rarely completed, but with occasional information) (Box 23)
    - R (miscellaneous) (Box 23)
    - Radio Stations, 5 folders (Box 23)
    - Rawson, Al (Box 23)
    - Religious Broadcasting (Box 23)
    - Richmond, Vincent (Box 23)
    - Robinson, Gordon D. (Box 23)
    - S (miscellaneous) (Box 23)
    - Salsbury, Buel (Box 23)
    - Schouten, John H. (Box 23)
    - Sherman, Harry (Mr. & Mrs.) (Box 23)
    - Speaking Engagements (Box 24)
    - Stickler, C.L. (Box 24)
    - T (miscellaneous) (Box 24)
    - Television Stations (Box 24)
    - Unions (general) (Box 24)
    - V (miscellaneous) (Box 24)
    - Van Osdoll, C.W. (Box 24)
    - W (miscellaneous) (Box 24)
    - Whirlpool Corp. (Box 24)
    - Woodward, J.W. (Box 24)
  - 1961-1962
    - A (miscellaneous) (Box 24)
    - Adverse
      - In district (Box 24)
      - Out of district (Box 24)
    - Austin, Faith (Box 24)
    - Ayers, Claude W. (Box 24)
    - B (miscellaneous) (Box 24)
    - Borush, John (Box 24)
    - Boyd, Leslie A. (Box 24)
    - Brady, Aubrey (Box 24)
    - C (miscellaneous) (Box 24)
    - Campbell, Keith (Box 24)
    - Christie, Hugh (Box 24)
    - Civil Rights (Box 24)
    - Collier, Irma (Box 24)
    - Commendatory
      - In district (Box 24)
      - Out of district (Box 24)
    - Communists-Communism (Box 24)
    - Complaints
      - Administration (Box 24)
      - Departments (Box 24)
      - Miscellaneous (Box 24)
    - Constitutional Educational League (Box 24)
    - D (miscellaneous) (Box 24)
    - Economy Party (Box 24)
    - F (miscellaneous) (Box 24)
    - Farm Labor (Box 24)
    - Fox, George R. (Box 24)
    - G (miscellaneous) (Box 24)
    - Granger, Fred L. (Box 24)
    - H (miscellaneous) (Box 24)
    - Hart, Merwin K. (Box 24)
    - Heibel, Cletus (Box 24)
    - Hoffman House Talks (responses to speeches and requests for copies)
      - General (Box 24)
      - Kennedy (Robert) (Box 24)